__
Show circle, everybody.
Welcome to Nationals.
I want you guys to remember something.
Glee Club is not about competition.
It's about something deeper.
Glee is about opening yourself up to joy.
Whoa...!
It's time.
Can't remember the last time
I was this nervous.
Oh, well, you don't look nervous at all.
You look great.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
20, count 'em,
20 of this nation's
And now we're down to the best of the best.
From Greenville, South
Carolina, the Harmony Busters.
From Lima, Ohio, the New Directions!
And from Portland, Oregon, the Soprano-gasms.
Only one of these amazing teams can claim the title
In third place,
And now, the first place winner
♪ ♪
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.MY-SUBS.com
Uh, uh, I-I'm sorry.
Would you mind saying that again?
I-I'm not sure
I understood you correctly.
The District Board of
Education has decided
In a very short time from now,
High School
Wh-Wh-What happened?
To be completely honest, Will,
Over the last decade,
Yeah.
And our quick fix was
Prioritizing what we would hope would be
You know what?
We were wrong.
Scores did not go up.
In fact, in some places, they got worse.
But you... you refused to let that stop you.
And I decided it was time for me to stick my neck out
And to my great surprise, they agreed with me.
Superintendent Harris, I mean... this is incredible news.
Please, please, if-if there's anything
I can do to help, just-just let me know.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna have you run the school.
Uh, I beg your pardon?
I'm making you principal, Will.
Congratulations.
Okay.
Wait, now, remember.
What? That cookie is for dessert.
Oh, come on.
Okay?
That is not an appetizer, all right?
Now that you're the principal, you have to set
I don't know if I can live up to that standard.
You're just gonna have to come have lunch with me
Oh, my goodness, Will.
Will...!
We have to do everything possible to be appropriate
I am never gonna have to worry
Our son will be in the day care that we set up in the gym.
And my beautiful wife
Oh, my goodness.
I'm so proud of you, Will.
It has been quite a journey to get to this place.
And you've made it the whole way without losing your integrity.
Except for those days when you were rapping.
Can I be honest with you about something?
I am scared to death.
Do I have the talent to actually do the job?
Will, you're the most talented man in the world.
Or at least in Ohio.
That's more like it.
Right.
I'm serious... you don't have anything to be scared about.
I'm not saying that it's gonna be easy,
Yeah.
...and be in love, right?
Because if we don't like something now, we can...
So no more bad guys.
It is just you and me
I love you so much.
I love you.
Now go get your son, Mr. Shue,
All right.
You see that, Danny?
Dreams really do come true.
Yeah.
Here he is!
Wow, um...
I have to say this is the most exciting first day
No offense to the alumni who have been here
Glee Club meeting.
All right, please, everyone, have a seat.
So, Mr. Shue when are you gonna start auditions?
Yeah, I think you're gonna have trouble sticking
Not true, Mr. Hummel.
The New Directions! will be only one
I'm bringing back the Troubletones
And we're also gonna have a junior varsity squad
So, wait, how are you gonna teach all those glee clubs
I'm not.
I'm actually not coaching any of them.
Not even the New Directions?
Well, uh, I've interviewed a...
But until then,
I wanted to say farewell to you all
My life changed...
And if I've learned one thing,
This is for you guys.
♪ You ♪
♪ Who are on the road ♪
♪ Must have a code ♪
♪ That you can live by ♪
♪ And so ♪
♪ Become yourself ♪
♪ Because the past ♪
♪ Is just a good-bye ♪
♪ Teach ♪
♪ Your children well ♪
♪ Their father's hell ♪
♪ Will slowly go by ♪
♪ And feed ♪
♪ Them on your dreams ♪
♪ The one they picks ♪
♪ The one you'll know by ♪
♪ Don't you ever ask them why ♪
♪ If they told you, you would cry ♪
♪ So just look at them and sigh... ♪
♪ And know they love you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Of tender years ♪
♪ Can't know the fears ♪
♪ That your elders grew by ♪
♪ And so please help ♪
♪ Them with your youth ♪
♪ They seek the truth ♪
♪ Before they can die ♪
♪ Teach ♪
♪ Your parents well ♪
♪ Their children's hell ♪
♪ Will slowly go by ♪
♪ And feed ♪
♪ Them on your dreams ♪
♪ The one they picks ♪
♪ The one you'll know by ♪
♪ Don't you ever ask them why ♪
♪ If they told you, you would cry ♪
♪ So just look at them and sigh... ♪
♪ And know they love you. ♪
Come on... a little...
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, uh, just a little inventory.
We got to do it before we sell all this stuff.
I mean, all these balls are under one PSI, so...
So listen, um,
I don't know, moving back to New York.
We have this spare room for you... it-it's perfect.
It's really small; it's more of, like, a closet, really, but...
Uh, yeah.
No, we talked about this before.
I told you that
New York's not my speed.
It's too fast; it's too loud;
We just root for whichever one's winning.
Okay, that's something
Kurt would say.
That's what happens when you get married.
Kurt and I are really happy, all right?
That's good. W-We're having a very good life together.
We see everybody...
We see Rachel,
Santana, Kitty...
It's a lot of fun, but I miss my best friend.
Dude, I miss you, too, man, you know?
But this is home, okay?
I need to be out in the wide-open spaces.
I need to be able to just go out on the weekends
Look, I'm happy.
I am genuinely happy here, okay?
This is where I'm meant to be.
I just don't want you to waste all of your talent.
I'm not... I'm using all of my talent in my new job.
All right.
Congratulations to all of you.
You have been selected as the best of the best.
You are this year's
New Directions!
Now I would like to introduce you all to your new teacher,
Mr. Sam Evans.
Wait, hold on, no.
Y-You're taking over the glee club?
Jealous?
Yeah.
I could not be more proud to pass the baton off to you.
Go get 'em, buddy.
All right, all right, all right.
So look,
I've been thinking a lot
This week, your assignment is...
...country!
Uh-oh.
Let's see where he goes with this.
Country and blues come from the same roots.
The hardship of a rural life.
Country uses little personal stories
Now, if we want to be great,
And even if we can't relate to the specifics,
So who wants to start us off with a country song?
Let's do "She Thinks
My Tractor's Sexy."
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, looks like we're all right where we belong.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
Okay, wait.
Stop right there.
I just want you guys to come in and listen,
Okay, I have officially been picked up
Effective immediately.
- Yay!
- I know.
You know, ever since I've been back,
I've just been walking these halls,
And the funny thing is...
It's getting really hard to remember that Mercedes.
Even when I got the call earlier,
I didn't think, "Oh, this must be some kind of mistake,"
"They must not mean me."
That's because of you guys.
Having friends like you really did change me.
You made me know that good things are possible.
It's not really... it's not really that common to come by...
No, no, no, no, do not come up here,
I am gonna lose it,
So, between
I won't be seeing you guys for a while.
Maybe even a-a long while.
You know, we'll keep in touch, but it's not gonna be the same,
So, I wanted to say good-bye my way... with a song.
And then, I want to walk out of here...
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ We'll be together ♪
♪ We'll be together, yeah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ You're far away ♪
♪ From me, my love ♪
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
♪ But just as sure, my, my baby ♪
♪ As there are stars above ♪
♪ I wanna say,
I wanna say, I wanna say ♪
♪ Someday we'll be together ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ We're gonna be together, be together, baby ♪
♪ We'll be together ♪
♪ We'll be together, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ A long time ago, my, my sweet thing ♪
♪ I made a big mistake, honey ♪
♪ I-I-I... say,
I-I-I-I said good-bye ♪
♪ Oh, oh, baby, ever ♪
♪ Ever ♪
♪ Ever and ever and ever and ever ♪
♪ Ever since that day now, now, now ♪
♪ All I ♪
♪ All I wanna do ♪
♪ Oh, is cry, cry, cry ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ I long for you ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, baby ♪
♪ Every, every night ♪
♪ Ooh, just to kiss your sweet, sweet lips, baby ♪
♪ Just to kiss your sweet lips ♪
♪ Hold you ever, ever so tight ♪
♪ I wanna say, ooh... ♪
♪ I wanna say ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
♪ We'll be together ♪
♪ Yeah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ooh, someday ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ We'll be together ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll be together, yes, we will ♪
♪ Ooh, someday ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ We'll be together ♪
♪ I, I-I-I-I-I, I know ♪
♪ Ooh, someday ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ We'll be together! ♪
Mercedes Jones has left the building.
Oh, hello, Porcelain.
Mrs. Porcelain.
What are you doing, Sue?
Well, I just came in to, uh,
But that seemed childish, so,
I, uh, just peed everywhere.
Can you have a seat for-for a second?
We wanted to talk to you.
As you probably already know,
Blaine and I are leaving for New York in a few days,
If it hadn't been for you,
So...
We really meant it: thank you.
Porcelain...
The first moment
I laid eyes on you,
I truly didn't understand what I was looking at.
With your hippo broaches
But then, I got to know you.
And even though you still constantly annoyed me,
I got to watch you go through what you went through.
The whole coming-out thing
I never knew
I had thoughts and feelings about those things
But you expanded my mind.
You taught me things about myself
And for that, I thank you.
Thank you.
Blaine...
I still don't really get you.
Um, I guess I just am not a fan of your thing.
But, hey,
Thank you, Sue.
I feel the same way about you.
And now, if you'll excuse me,
I was coming to see you!
I was coming to see you, too!
Oh!
Coach, I'm sorry that I said
Oh, honey, I'm the one who's sorry.
I've been treating you like an unpaid intern,
But honey, there's still one last person I have to see.
- All right.
- All right, babe.
Hey, Sue.
You wanted to see me?
Uh, what's... what's going on?
♪ I don't wanna talk ♪
♪ About things we've gone through ♪
♪ Nothing more to say ♪
♪ No more ace to play ♪
♪ The winner takes it all ♪
♪ The loser's standing small ♪
♪ Beside the victory ♪
♪ That's her destiny ♪
♪ But tell me, does she kiss ♪
♪ Like I used to kiss you? ♪
♪ Does it feel the same ♪
♪ When she calls your name? ♪
Butt Chin...
♪ The game is on again ♪
♪ A lover or a friend ♪
♪ A big thing or a small ♪
♪ The winner takes it all ♪
♪ I don't wanna talk ♪
♪ If it makes you feel sad ♪
♪ And I understand ♪
♪ You've come to shake my hand ♪
♪ The winner takes it all... ♪
♪ The winner takes it all ♪
♪ The loser has to fall ♪
♪ The winner takes ♪
♪ It all! ♪
Look, I know why you want...
Brad!
__
Snipers stand down.
Pocahontas has landed.
Welcome back, everybody.
President Jeb Bush will win the crucial battleground state
With me now, before she heads down to Times Square
Sue Sylvester.
Madam Vice President, thank you so much for being here.
Well, thank you, Geraldo.
And I just spoke to the president,
Now, Madam Vice President,
I have to ask you,
You bet your sweet ass, Geraldo.
Well, folks, you heard it here first... the vice president.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations to you.
We'll be back with more election night coverage right after this.
I wanted to make a time capsule of my time at McKinley.
I know it's stupid, but it'd give me a reason to come back every once in a while.
Oh, it's really, really sweet.
I have programs
Horror Picture Show wig,
Finn, and oh, prom queen crown...
Wh...
Wh-Why are you crying and laughing at the same time?
Because you're the only person I know
You're the only one.
And-and that is why
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
♪ ♪
Kids, we have two very special guests here
Kurt Hummel and Blaine Anderson are coming,
Recently, they performed the first LGBTQ version
Woolf at Lincoln Center.
So please give a warm,
Harvey Milk
Elementary School welcome
Hello.
We are so excited to be here.
It is so cool to be in a place where it's safe
It kind of reminds us of our school.
Mm-hmm.
Or at least one room in our school.
And that was called the choir room.
Now that's because we had
Yeah. So we want to encourage all of you guys to be
♪ Oh, I could hide
'neath the wings ♪
♪ Of the bluebird as she sings ♪
♪ The six o'clock alarm ♪
♪ Would never ring ♪
♪ But it rings and I rise ♪
♪ Wipe the sleep out of my eyes ♪
♪ My shaving razor's cold ♪
♪ And it stings ♪
♪ Cheer up, Sleepy Jean ♪
♪ Oh, what can it mean ♪
♪ To a daydream believer ♪
♪ And a homecoming queen ♪
♪ You once thought of me ♪
♪ As a white knight on his steed ♪
♪ Now you know how happy ♪
♪ I can be ♪
♪ Oh, and our good times start and end ♪
♪ Without dollar one to spend ♪
♪ But how much, baby ♪
♪ Do we really need ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh! ♪
♪ Cheer up, Sleepy Jean ♪
♪ Oh, what can it mean ♪
♪ To a daydream believer ♪
♪ And a ♪
♪ Homecoming queen ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Cheer up, Sleepy Jean ♪
♪ Oh, what can it mean ♪
♪ To a daydream believer ♪
♪ And a homecoming queen ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
Hands in, everybody.
Hands in, hands in, hands in.
Amazing!
♪ These walls ♪
♪ And all these picture frames ♪
♪ Every name ♪
♪ They show ♪
♪ These halls ♪
♪ I've walked a thousand times ♪
♪ Heartbreaks and valentines ♪
♪ Friends of mine all know ♪
♪ I look at everything I was ♪
♪ And everything I ever loved ♪
♪ And I can see how much I've grown ♪
♪ I'm not afraid ♪
♪ Of moving on and letting go ♪
♪ It's just so hard to say good-bye ♪
♪ To what I know ♪
♪ This time no one's gonna say good-bye
♪ I keep you in this heart of mine ♪
♪ This time that we had ♪
♪ I will hold ♪
♪ Forever... ♪
♪ This old ♪
♪ Familiar place is ♪
♪ Where every face is ♪
♪ Another part of me ♪
♪ I played a different game then ♪
♪ They called me a different name then ♪
♪ I think of all the things I did ♪
♪ And how I wish I knew what I know now ♪
♪ I see how far I've come ♪
♪ And what I got right ♪
♪ When I was looking for that spotlight ♪
♪ I was looking for myself ♪
♪ Got over what
I was afraid of ♪
♪ I showed 'em all that I was made of ♪
♪ More than trophies on a shelf ♪
♪ For all the battles that we lost ♪
♪ Or might have won ♪
♪ I never stopped believing ♪
♪ In the words we sung ♪
♪ We sung ♪
♪ This time no one's gonna say good-bye ♪
♪ I keep you in this heart of mine ♪
♪ This time that we had ♪
♪ I will hold ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ I'm looking out ♪
♪ From the crossroads ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ How far away I will roll ♪
♪ I take a breath ♪
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ And your voice will carry me ♪
♪ Home... ♪
♪ I keep you in this heart of mine ♪
♪ This time I know ♪
♪ It's never over ♪
♪ No matter who or what I am ♪
♪ I'll carry where we all began ♪
♪ This time that we had ♪
♪ I will hold ♪
♪ I will hold... ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Forever. ♪
Mercedes!
We have amazing news.
Remember that movie that Artie wrote for you but you were
Well, it got into
Sundance Film Festival.
No, Tina, I told you it got into Slamdance.
Also, big favor, Mercedes.
We want to use your songs for the soundtrack.
Oh, my agent usually handles that.
I am kidding. You can have whatever song you like.
- Guys, come on. We're gonna be late.
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, did you hear about Sam?
He already has a new girlfriend.
Can you believe that?
Come on, I don't want to miss a moment.
Well, then, why does he keep texting me?
Knock, knock.
Come in!
Is it time already?
It's time!
We're all here!
- Hi! We're here!
- Hey, Rachel!
Oh, no, don't strain yourself.
Please. I've been sweating my boobs off
This baby can have my body now,
Mama wants it back.
Well, we got you some, uh, organic juice
Thank you. It's supposed to help the baby's brain grow.
Okay, hold on. So, I've heard this story from Kurt and Blaine,
What in the heck made you say
"yes" to being their surrogate?
Obviously, there's a full-circle story based on how I was raised,
And I figured, they've given up so much of their lives
The least I could do was give them nine months of mine.
Hi.
Oh, I love you guys so much.
You're gonna be the most amazing dads.
I can't wait for that.
Oh, here's my husband!
Because I'm ready to get started
So romantic.
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Okay.
Wish us luck, you guys.
Bye, your guys.
Break a leg.
Bye.
You guys, we'll be praying...
Bye. Have fun.
Fingers crossed.
So, as a former Tony winner,
I feel like I need to give you some pointers
I'm not gonna win. Yes, you are.
You are gonna win.
Really? Okay.
So, when you get up there,
Well, he is pretty amazing and handsome,
Here we are.
- You okay?
- Whew. Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Best Actress in a Musical...
...please welcome Broadway's very own Andrew Rannells.
Bad dog!
Hey.
- Oh.
- Oh, my gosh.
The nominees for...
- Oh. Here we go... - Best
Actress in a Musical are:
Maggie Smith in Miss Jean
Brodie's Second Prime.
Willow Smith in Cabaret.
Anne Hathaway in her one-woman show,
Anne! exclamation point.
And Rachel Berry in Jane Austen Sings.
And the Tony goes to...
Rachel Berry
Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, I, um... I-I want
And I want to thank my
Okay, I want to thank...
Carmen Tibideaux at NYADA
Um, but I want to dedicate this award
Um, Mr. Shue always taught to my strengths
And he picked me up when I was in a million pieces.
He taught me the one great thing that all teachers do,
And that is, being a part of something special
Something is special because you are a part of it.
Mr. Shue, I love you so much.
And to all of the boys and girls out there,
I just want to say quickly before I walk off the stage,
__
Ladies and gentlemen, the Vice
President of the United States.
Fantastic.
Becky? Becky?!
It's okay, honey.
He's clean.
You know, a great big fat person once stood on this stage
Now, it's no secret that for a long time,
I thought that was a load of hooey.
As far as I can see, the glee club is nothing more
You know what?
I was exactly right.
But I was wrong about the cowardly part.
What I finally realize,
It takes
A world where the quarterback becomes best friends
Glee is about imagining a world like that,
That's what Glee Club is.
And for the longest time,
I thought that was silly.
And now, I think it's just about the bravest thing
I'm honored to be here to rededicate this theater
William, it is with your hard work,
McKinley High School for the Performing Arts
Congratulations, Will Schuester.
You and your little Glee Club
And now, without further ado,
♪ Bah, bah, bah, bah ♪
♪ Hope you take that jump ♪
♪ Bah, bah... ♪
♪ You don't fear the fall ♪
♪ Bah, bah ♪
♪ Bah, bah, bah, bah ♪
♪ Hope when the water rises ♪
♪ Bah, bah... ♪
♪ You built a wall ♪
♪ Bah, bah ♪
♪ Bah, bah, bah, bah ♪
♪ Hope when crowd screams out ♪
♪ Bah, bah, bah... ♪
♪ They're screaming your name ♪
♪ Bah, bah, bah ♪
♪ Bah, bah ♪
♪ Hope if everybody runs ♪
♪ You choose to stay ♪
♪ Bah, bah, bah, bah ♪
♪ I hope that you fall in love ♪
♪ Bah-bah, bah-bah ♪
♪ And it hurts so bad ♪
♪ Bah, bah ♪
♪ Yeah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Bah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Bah, bah ♪
♪ The only way you can know, you give it all you have ♪
♪ Hey, yeah ♪
♪ Bah-bah, bah-bah ♪
♪ And I hope that you don't suffer ♪
♪ But take the pain ♪
♪ Bah-bah, bah-bah, bah-bah ♪
♪ Bah-bah, bah-bah, bah ♪
♪ Hope when the moment comes ♪
♪ You'll say ♪
♪ I, I, I ♪
♪ I did it all ♪
♪ I owned every second that this world could give ♪
♪ I saw so many places, the things that I did ♪
♪ With every broken bone ♪
♪ I swear I lived ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh-oh-oh, oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey-ey-ey ♪
♪ With every broken bone ♪
♪ I lived... ♪
♪ I, I, I ♪
♪ I did it all ♪
♪ I did it all, yeah ♪
♪ I owned every second that this world could give ♪
♪ This world could give ♪
♪ I saw so many places, the things that I did ♪
♪ Yeah, with every broken bone ♪
♪ I swear I lived ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah-ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I swear I lived ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Mm, mm-mm ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh-oh-oh! ♪
♪ Mm, mm-mm-mm-mm. ♪
Amazing!
__
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.MY-SUBS.com